So type hotel
But everything was full
So they got to sleep instead in a stable
There Mary gave birth to his son, Jesus
At the same time on a meadow near the stable
were there any shepherds guarding their sheep
Then mittyjall, the whole sky was lit up in a strong glow and they became scared
An angel said:
Tadaa
Don't be afraid, I come with super good news to you
and to the whole world
Tonight the God's own Son has been born
He is your rescuer, Messiah
And he lies wrapped in a crib
and, yes, you will find him there
Glory be God in height and peace on the whole earth, Jo
The shepherds wandered to the stable and praised the newborn Jesus
In another country there were some star interpreters
Some show men simply
"When you found the king, then come and tell me that
so that I can also pay tribute to him ”
The wise men nodded
and continued to look for the new king
They finally found the stable and gave presents to Jesus
They gave gold, incense and myrrh
In this way was born and celebrated Jesus
And that is why we celebrate Christmas
In short, it's Jesus' birthday
But what happened to herod then
Well, an angel said to the wise men
Not to tell Herod
So he never found Jesus
Okay
Well then it was clear!
Like that, now we have got our memories refreshed